

# MOHD. SHADAB

APPLICATION DEVELOPMENT ANALYST

# ABOUT ME

I am a qualified and professional web developer/App. development analyst with 1.9 years of experience in front-end web development, agile, dev-ops, and QA. I have strong creative and analytical skills. I am a team player with an eye for detail.

## WORK EXPERIENCE

## < APPLICATION DEVELOPMENT ANALYST >

Accenture Pvt. Ltd.

Jun 2022 - Present

I have worked on two **E-Commerce projects** in my 1.9 years of tenure. I worked with the Development and QA team to deliver the best results for tough clients working in **B2C** web order to increase the omnichannel engagement for the Belgian market i.e. handling their French & Dutch websites on **SAP Hybris Platform**.

For my other project, I handled **52 global** websites for a multinational fashion holding company by helping them migrate from Oracle Atg to **Salesforce Business Manager** and their other subsidiaries.

#### < ASSOCIATE SOFTWARE ENGINEER >

Accenture Pvt. Ltd.

Feb 2021 - Jun 2022

After graduation, I joined as an associate software engineer and got trained in various technologies like

Web Development (Html, CSS, JS), SQL and Agile Methodologies, Dev-ops, etc. for 6 Months along with this I was assigned to a client project for project-based learning to get real corporate exposure.

#### < TECH INTERN (FRONT-END) >

NDTV Convergence Ltd. Jun 2018 - Jul 2018

Worked on modifying the UI of sales management system software using front-end tools like Html/CSS & Bootstrap. Worked with the Ad tech. dept. by testing the functionalities of ads on various devices before they were live on the website.

# **NOTABLE ACHIEVEMENTS**

- Awarded the "Best Performer" award twice from my leads at Accenture
- Awarded the "Exemplify Client-Centricity" award by the leadership for my contribution to the project at Accenture.
- Awarded the "Best People" award for my contribution to the project at Accenture.
- Our team was awarded "The Extra Mile Award" in the Offshore - Team category for its outstanding contribution to the organization at Accenture.

# CONTACTS

in www.linkedin.com/in/heyshadab

github.com/Shadab05

shadabfeb@gmail.com

+91-8349851369

Bhopal, M.P, India

# **PROJECTS**

< CAPRI HOLDINGS LTD. >

Aug 2022 - Present

#### MULTINATIONAL FASHION HOLDING COMPANY

- Michael Kors, Versace, and Jimmy Choo are the brands of Capri Holdings, a marketer, distributor, and retailer of upscale accessories and apparel.
- Handling the 52 global E-Commerce websites of Michael Kors and their other subsidiaries i.e. Versace and Jimmy Choo for different locales.
  Performing smoke testing and validating the performance and integrity of the sites globally.
- Helping them migrate their business from Atg to Salesforce Commerce Cloud BM which helps maintain multiple sites by using a single system to manage all customer engagement channels.

#### < CARREFOUR GROUP >

Jun 2021 - Aug 2022

# FRENCH MULTINATIONAL RETAIL COMPANY

- Carrefour is one of the largest retailers in the world.
- I worked on the SAP Hybris platform for B2C web orders, handling the clients to fulfill their needs and achieving on-time deliveries.
- Handing sanity for the French & Dutch websites intended to increase the omnichannel engagement for the Belgian market.
- Worked on SAP Hybris Backoffice administration cockpit for store configuration, Hybris promotions, SAP promotions, slot creations, etc.
- Creating and raising the defects and uploading the test cases on JIRA.
- Followed the agile methodologies to achieve our sprint targets and also handled the smoke testing for the production environment verifying seamless build and its integrity.

## EDUCATION

#### < Oriental Institute of Science and Technology>

**B.E in Information Technology** 

2016 - 2020

SGPA (8th Semester) - 9.25 | CGPA - 8.05

> Graduated with first division ( HONOURS )

#### < St. Montfort School, Bhopal > 2009 - 2016

> Class 12th - 2016 | Percentage- 71.6%

## SKILLS

#### < CODING & SCRIPTING LANGUAGES >

- C+
- HTML / CSS
- JAVASCRIPT
- PYTHON
- LINUX
- SQL (ORACLE)

### < FRAMEWORKS/SYSTEMS/SOFTWARES >

- VISUAL STUDIO
- BOOTSTRAP
- REACT JS
- MS EXCEL
- MS POWERPOINT

#### < SOFT SKILLS >

- ATTENTION TO DETAIL
- TIME MANAGEMENT
- TEAMWORK
- COMMUNICATION & CREATIVITY

## PORTFOLIO

https://iamshadab.ml/

